

Contact

Phone +995 595 033 062

Email Eqizashvili16@gmail.com

Address Tbilisi, Georgia

LinkedIn Link

Portfolio Link

Github

Vercel Link

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React.js
- Next.js
- Tailwindcss
- Bootstrap
- Git and Github

Language

English (B2)

German (A2)

Russian (fluent)

Georgian (Mother tongue)

Mariam Ekizashvili

Frontend developer

I am a 20-year-old frontend developer with two years of experience in this field, namely React and Next.js. I create beautiful websites and apps that adapt to all devices. All my projects are designed by me.

By engaging in various volunteer projects, I have demonstrated effective collaboration and problem-solving skills. I am motivated and adaptable, I always try to learn new technologies in the field and bring them into my work.

In addition to technical skills, I have a disciplined, results-oriented mindset. I work freely under tight deadlines. I have a clear way of speaking and a strong sense of responsibility.

Experience

June 2023 - Present

Youth Society Parzival

Mern stack Development

As the sole developer of the Parzival team, I'm responsible for developing and refining the website using Next.js, MongoDB and related technologies. My role involves developing visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces. In close collaboration with Parzival members, I discuss project ideas. My responsibility is to continuously update the site to keep the website dynamic and optimized.

Jan. 2023 - Present

m2 - Developer Company

Frontend Development

I work remotely for a growing Georgian company located in Russia as a frontend developer. Like Parzival, I am the only developer, where I am responsible for collecting information about the company, developing a pleasant interface and ensuring the functionality of the website. I work in Next.js. The website is under development.

Education

Feb. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Davit Kenchadze's Front-End course

I undertook a year-long course that commenced in February 2023 and concluded prematurely in December. The reason for the early completion was my transition to a more advanced group that had started three months earlier. This shift resulted from my proactive approach, completing tasks ahead of schedule, and showcasing advanced skills compared to my peers. Throughout the course, I acquired expertise in Responsive Web Development, Bootstrap, Advanced Javascript, and React.js.

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023

Introduction to Computer Science in JavaScript (Golden)

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Responsive Web Design (FreeCodeCamp)

Dec 2023 - Present

• The Complete JavaScript Course 2024: From Zero to Expert!